Mighty Little Defenders 11 – New Wild Cosmos.
Shining Golden Bulala
Episode 13
Everyone
Give up. No one can help you today.
Are you scared? It’s not over yet.
you two
Yes, yes.
Please remove his Knot for me
Master Quan, he is the King after all.
Isn’t that good?
Now I’m the King, do it to me
No I can’t treat a good King like this
His Majesty is our real King
Stubborn old men who are ignorant of current affairs
Remember that from now on
there is only one King
and that’s me
Whoever dares to disobey my order
will end up the same as him
No
stop
What
You are finally here
what’s going on
They both have elemental power
What kind of power is this? It’s so powerful.
This is thanks to our return to the Thorn Forest.
Since these thunder Bulala and rain Bulala are also Bulala
We can definitely eat it too
Red Bulala will burn
Then try something else
Very good, got around it
Come together
I won’t back down this time
are you okay
I’m fine
I just feel so tired
my hand
What’s wrong? What’s wrong with your hand?
you look at me you look at me
So magical, so magical
I saw
I seem to
as well
Such powerful energy
I don’t know how long this energy can last
There’s so much more here
If it’s gone, eat it again
But how to take these Bulala away?
wait for me
That’s it
Just open this vent
All the Bulala here will be blown into the town
Then let’s get started
Weslie
So dangerous
you see
we succeeded
I didn’t expect that the element Bulala could be used in this way
but
You can’t win against me with this kind of thing
Take Father out of here
No, I want to come too
I didn’t expect you to be quite powerful.
But in the face of my strongest power
All your efforts are in vain
It should be safe here
It doesn’t matter to me. You go and help them.
Don’t worry, the king will be protected by us. It’ll be okay.
let’s go
it’s over
take advantage of now
Do you think you can defeat me like this? You are so naïve
If we continue fighting like this, not only will we not be able to defeat him
I’m afraid the entire Bulala world will be destroyed
Have you found out
The light on Uncle’s chest
Will it
be the key
Do you want to eat so much at one time?
Sparky
Still not giving up
Then I will make you completely despair.
It’s dangerous, get away quickly
Sparky, wake up soon
I want to protect Sparky
Give up, all the Bulala here are for me
Sparky
Uncle, I must stop you
Has Sparky succeeded?
It’s a colorful fragment
Maybe if you take it away you won’t have the power anymore.
You actually want to take my piece
No one can take it away
Wolffy, it’s up to you.
Leave it to me
No; let go quickly
Take advantage now Weslie
Overestimating your capabilities
We are here to help too
So what if there are just two more wires?
who said that
Don’t underestimate us
Don’t bully Brother Weslie
Let’s come too
Come on everyone
Not good
What
Wolffy
no one can beat me
No hope
don’t give up
Everyone must pool their strength
Like twisting threads together to become a rope
That’s right if we twist all the wires together
We will definitely become stronger
That’s right, my subjects.
we need to unite again
No matter how united the ants are, they are just ants.
How could it be possible to win me?
Everyone, listen to my order: launch
Everyone, work hard
Why no response?
This is the power of unity
Impossible. I am invincible.
Come on, we’re almost there
I love frying pan
He has no power. Now!
Wolffy
Everyone turned golden
Father, could this be
The legendary Golden Bulala?
This is what I saw on the top of the Thorn Mountain
I saw that everyone was united
to build this beautiful place
I found
This is the Golden Bulala I’ve been looking for
Golden Bulala is a spirit of our Bulala Kingdom
As long as Golden Bulala exists
Our Bulala Kingdom will be full of vitality
Never give up
Look
It turns out that Golden Bulala really exists
So beautiful
Uncle
Uncle, are you okay?
I hope Master Quan can change his ways
and make up for his own mistakes
It’s that monster
Gone
That fragment is so dangerous
Just snatched away
Sparky said that monster is not from this world
Could it be related to the rift ?
This way, this way
I didn’t expect the city to be repaired so quickly
It feels like this place is more beautiful than when we first arrived.
Weslie, look over there
Everyone is using the element Bulala
It feels so good to feel everyone is united
All thanks to you
It’s you who unite all the residents of Bulala
We will send you here
Do you also want to return to your own world?
It says it likes it here
it wants to stay
Then we go back
This rift is dangerous
You should be careful
In order to prevent monsters from entering
We’ll have soldiers hold this place
With the ability of elemental Bulala
it’s no problem
Then we can leave with peace of mind
We believe we will meet again, right?
Yes
We will definitely meet again
goodbye
Goodbye friends
here you go
go ahead
Get the fragments from other places as well
To be continued